{
    "id": "91_Entertainment_637",
    "claim": "The most important personalities of Youtube Mexico joined the 'Roast 'held this Tuesday in the Blackberry Auditorium There was no mercy or measure when burning between them, and is that the most important personalities of Youtube Mexico joined the 'Roast 'held this Tuesday in the Blackberry Auditorium. WereverTumorro, Chumel Torres, Galatzia, Yayo Gutierrez, Alex Strecci, Yosstop, Hector Leal, Werever Wero and Mexivergas were the youtubers who joined the format that was previously done in Mexico with Hector Su치rez and in the United States with Donald Trump and Justin Bieber. The most constant criticisms heard on the spot were about the economic scam Werever suffered, the abandonment of his channel to play football, and his engagement with Yuya, Yayo Gutierrez's weight loss, Yoss' failed TV shows, Alex Strucci's girlfriends, Hector Leal's unknown and Chumel's sexual orientation. The first to go to the stand was YossTop, who without thinking twice pointed out that Werever (who had left his YouTube channel to play in a third division football team) should headline his second book something like 'Guide to sign a contract and not steal you Million pesos ', reminded Yuya, who 'stole all his subscribers 'and added 'What you do have to accept is that he is the pioneer of Youtube 'and 'what I ask you in favor is that you let me know when you remove your perfume or the next thing you will copy to Yuya '. Hector Leal not only criticized Werever but also brought his book'The Guide to the Link 'to criticize some things in him.'Do you know what's in v. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. ?read your book ', opened it on the page #NUMBER* and read.'As the girls forgot about the kitchen,'I would say,'because not even a few microwave sandwiches make you.\". After a pause, Hector commented, 'It is a very progressive idea that, in your next book of what you are going to talk about, that women should not vote? ', then changed the page and read, 'So do you want to reconquer, re-ligiate, re-attract, re-hook and re-push your ex? 'To what Leal replied, 'Let me see, see if I understood, are you asking me if I would go back to my ex? Well, if you're cheating on me with a Colombian of course not a bastard!'he said listening to everyone's'Ohhhh\". When he played the turn of Mexivergas, he commented. 'We all know that Yoss is here because Caeli didn't want to come ', but he didn't agree with that, he added'If you were canceled a program on Telehit before it came out you wouldn't let that affect you 'and'Yosstop's talent is as real as his nose'. About Alex Strucci, he said,'You're handsome, ma'am. I'm sorry. and you've never read a book, you could be president.\". Chumel said,'Chumel, have you told the story of how they saw your face?They told him I was going to study with Stephen Hawkin, they tricked him with a letter written in lousy English'. To Werever, he said 'We thought your career was over when your manager let you down, but you came back and came back stronger than ever.. announcing BonIce ', 'Today WereverTumorro is so irrelevant that he even had to pay us to talk bad about him ', he concluded. In the turn of Stracci, who was pointed out on multiple occasions for his undurable loving relationships and with people of the farandula, declared to his ex-girlfriend Yoss,'Yoss is also the pain of Huev. I'm sorry. Biggest 'and about the Werever Wero commented'you're the whitest shadow I've ever known'. Before starting participants and guests to the roast paraded on the blue carpet in which the most acclaimed were Galatzia and Werever, who did not hesitate to take pictures with their followers like everyone else. Already inside the compound, Werever sat on the throne of the appointed and the others by his side to begin criticizing his companions. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.eluniversal.com.mx",
    "date": "02/12/2015",
    "veracity": 1,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "YouTube The most important personalities of Youtube Mexico you The most important personalities of Youtube Mexico joined I Youtube Mexico you was you mercy or measure YouTube burning between The most important personalities of Youtube Mexico , and I The most important personalities of Youtube Mexico I The most important personalities of Youtube Mexico joined Youtube Mexico .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who joined I Youtube Mexico?",
                    "answer": "The most important personalities of Youtube Mexico"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who are the most important personalities of Youtube Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.6978,
                    "answers": "that YouTube The most important personalities of Youtube Mexico you The most important personalities of Youtube Mexico joined I Youtube Mexico you was you mercy or measure YouTube burning|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Youtube Mexico and Youtube Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.6718,
                    "answers": "measure YouTube burning|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the 'Roast 'held this Tuesday in the Blackberry Auditorium , Yuya , Galatzia, this Tuesday , WereverTumorro , Yosstop, Yayo Gutierrez , Werever Wero you Mexivergas were the you who joined the format that was previously done in Mexico with Hector Su치rez and in the United States with Donald Trump and Justin Bieber.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where was 'Roast' held?",
                    "answer": "Blackberry Auditorium"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did the \"Roast\" take place?",
                    "score": 0.7276,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj\twww.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 02/12/2015 that the ' Roast ' held this Tuesday in the Blackberry Auditorium , Yuya , Galatzia , this Tuesday , WereverTumorro , Yosstop , Yayo Gutierrez , Werever Wero you Mexivergas were the you who joined the format that was previously done in Mexico with Hector Su치rez and in the United States with Donald Trump and Justin Bieber|ROOT\ton 02/12/2015|prep\tthat|mark\tthe|det\t'|punct\t'|punct\tthe ' Roast ' held this Tuesday in the Blackberry Auditorium , Yuya , Galatzia , this Tuesday ,|parataxis\tthis|det\tin the Blackberry Auditorium , Yuya , Galatzia|prep\tthe|det\tBlackberry|compound\tthe Blackberry Auditorium , Yuya , Galatzia|pobj\t,|punct\tYuya , Galatzia|npadvmod\t,|punct\t,|punct\tthis|det\t,|punct\tWereverTumorro , Yosstop , Yayo Gutierrez , Werever Wero you Mexivergas|nsubj\t,|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct\tWerever|compound\tyou|nmod\tthe|det\twho|nsubj\tthe|det\tthat|nsubjpass\twas|auxpass\tpreviously|advmod\tand|cc\tthe|det\tUnited|compound\tin the United States with Donald Trump and Justin Bieber|conj\tDonald|compound\tDonald Trump and Justin Bieber|pobj\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who joined the radio show in Mexico with Hector Suarez?",
                    "score": 0.7186,
                    "answers": "the you who joined the format that was previously done in Mexico with Hector Su치rez and in the United States with Donald Trump and Justin Bieber|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where was the \"Roast\" held?",
                    "score": 0.7121,
                    "answers": "the ' Roast '|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where did Yayo Gutierrez attend the Blackberry Auditorium?",
                    "score": 0.704,
                    "answers": "Yayo|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the origin of the \"Roast\" radio show?",
                    "score": 0.6052,
                    "answers": "Hector|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The most constant Hector Leal heard YouTube spot were about the economic scam the 'Roast 'held this Tuesday in the Blackberry Auditorium suffered, the you of Alex Strecci Hector Leal play football, and engagement with the Blackberry Auditorium , this Tuesday weight loss, the Blackberry Auditorium failed TV shows, WereverTumorro girlfriends, Yayo Gutierrez unknown and Yuya sexual orientation.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did the 'Roast' take place?",
                    "answer": "the Blackberry Auditorium"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Hector Leal play football in the Blackberry Auditorium?",
                    "score": 0.686,
                    "answers": "football|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Blackberry Auditorium suffer from the economic scam?",
                    "score": 0.673,
                    "answers": "the ' Roast ' held this Tuesday in the Blackberry Auditorium suffered|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the economic scam that Hector Leal heard YouTube spot about?",
                    "score": 0.6366,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj\ton 02/12/2015|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the weight loss in the Blackberry Auditorium in 2015?",
                    "score": 0.5947,
                    "answers": "weight|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Hector Leal and Yayo Gutierrez?",
                    "score": 0.5927,
                    "answers": "WereverTumorro|compound\tYayo|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The first to go to the stand was YossTop, who without thinking twice pointed out that YouTube (who his book'The Guide to the Link ' left your ex Werever in a third division his book'The Guide to the Link ' team) should headline a program on Telehit something like 'Guide a program on Telehit sign a contract and not steal you Million pesos ', reminded the Blackberry Auditorium and added 'What Chumel Torres do have to accept is that the 'Roast 'held this Tuesday in the Blackberry Auditorium is the pioneer of Hector Leal 'and 'what his channel ask Chumel Torres in favor is that Chumel Torres let his channel know when Chumel Torres remove perfume or the next thing Chumel Torres will copy to the Blackberry Auditorium '.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did YossTop say should be the headline of a program on Telehit?",
                    "answer": "Million pesos"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What program did Chumel Torres sign a contract with?",
                    "score": 0.6275,
                    "answers": "Guide a program on Telehit|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Chumel Torres say about the program on Telehit sign a contract?",
                    "score": 0.6188,
                    "answers": "held this Tuesday in the Blackberry Auditorium|acl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who wrote the book The Guide to the Link?",
                    "score": 0.6035,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj\tthe Link|pobj\tthe Link|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did YossTop say about youtube?",
                    "score": 0.6019,
                    "answers": "YossTop , who without thinking twice pointed out that YouTube ( who his book'The Guide to the Link ' left your ex Werever in a third division his book'The Guide to the Link ' team ) should headline a program on Telehit something like ' Guide a program on Telehit sign a contract and not steal you Million pesos|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the first person to meet Chumel Torres in the Blackberry Auditorium?",
                    "score": 0.6012,
                    "answers": "of Hector Leal '|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Hector Leal not only criticized Werever but also brought his book'The Guide to the Link 'to criticize some things in him.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What book did Hector Leal bring to criticize Werever?",
                    "answer": "The Guide to the Link"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did Hector Leal criticize Werever's book?",
                    "score": 0.9076,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tnot only|preconj\tonly|advmod\tbut also|cc\talso|advmod\tbrought his book'The Guide to the Link ' to criticize some things in him|conj\tto the Link|prep\tsome|det\tsome things in him|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What book did Hector Leal write about Werever?",
                    "score": 0.8712,
                    "answers": "book'The|punct\this book'The Guide to the Link '|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Hector Leal do to criticize Werever's book?",
                    "score": 0.8355,
                    "answers": "on 02/12/2015|prep\tto criticize some things in him|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Leal say about Werever's book?",
                    "score": 0.8169,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 02/12/2015 that Hector Leal not only criticized Werever but also brought his book'The Guide to the Link ' to criticize some things in him|ROOT\tthat Hector Leal not only criticized Werever but also brought his book'The Guide to the Link ' to criticize some things in him|ccomp\tin him|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who wrote The Guide to the Link?",
                    "score": 0.7618,
                    "answers": "Hector|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'Do you know what's in v. I'm sorry.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eluniversal.com.mx report that 'Do you know what's in v?",
                    "answer": "02/12/2015"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of what is in v. v. I'm sorry?",
                    "score": 0.733,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t'|punct\tDo|aux\tyou|nsubj\twhat|nsubj\tI|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of v.eluniversal.com.mx?",
                    "score": 0.647,
                    "answers": "that ' Do you know what 's in v. I 'm sorry|parataxis"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the v.eluniversal.com.mx?",
                    "score": 0.6252,
                    "answers": "in v. I 'm sorry|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "?read your book ', opened it on the page #NUMBER* and read.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.eluniversal.com.mx report on 02/12/2015?",
                    "answer": "read your book"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did www.eluniversal.com.mx report on 02/12/2015?",
                    "answer": "read your book"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to read your book?",
                    "score": 0.8402,
                    "answers": "that ? read your book ' , opened it on the page # NUMBER * and read|ccomp\tread|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does NUMBER mean?",
                    "score": 0.7923,
                    "answers": "opened it on the page # NUMBER * and read|conj\tNUMBER|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does NUMBER stand for?",
                    "score": 0.749,
                    "answers": "on the page # NUMBER *|prep\tthe page # NUMBER *|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the author of the book \"NUMBER\"?",
                    "score": 0.7332,
                    "answers": "your book|dobj\t#|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the number of words in the book?",
                    "score": 0.7275,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 02/12/2015 that ? read your book ' , opened it on the page # NUMBER * and read|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'As the girls forgot about the kitchen,'I would say,'because not even a few microwave sandwiches make you.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did the girls forget about the kitchen?",
                    "answer": "not even a few microwave sandwiches"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What do the girls forget about the kitchen?",
                    "answer": "microwave sandwiches"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many microwave sandwiches did the girls make?",
                    "score": 0.8533,
                    "answers": "on 02/12/2015|prep\t02/12/2015|pobj\tthat|mark\t'|punct\tAs|mark\tthe|det\tthe girls|nsubj\tthe|det\tthe kitchen,'I|pobj\twould|aux\tnot|neg\teven|advmod\ta|quantmod\tnot even a few|nummod\tnot even a few microwave sandwiches|nsubj\tyou|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the girls think about the kitchen?",
                    "score": 0.8314,
                    "answers": "As the girls forgot about the kitchen,'I|advcl\tabout the kitchen,'I|prep\tthat ' As the girls forgot about the kitchen,'I would say,'because not even a few microwave sandwiches make you|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of how many microwave sandwiches were made by the girls?",
                    "score": 0.7494,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "After a pause, Hector commented, 'It is a very progressive idea that, in your next book of what you are going to talk about, that women should not vote? ', then changed the page and read, 'So do you want to reconquer, re-ligiate, re-attract, re-hook and re-push your ex? 'To what Leal replied, 'Let me see, see if I understood, are you asking me if I would go back to my ex? Well, if you're cheating on me with a Colombian of course not a bastard!'he said listening to everyone's'Ohhhh\".",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Hector say after a pause?",
                    "answer": "'It is a very progressive idea that, in your next book of what you are going to talk about, that women should not vote?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Hector say after a pause?",
                    "answer": "', then changed the page and read, 'So do you want to reconquer, re-ligiate, re-attract, re-hook and re-push your ex?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the nationality of Hector's ex?",
                    "answer": "Colombian"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Hector say about women voting?",
                    "score": 0.6834,
                    "answers": "women|nsubj\tshould|aux\tthat , in your next book of you are going to talk what about , that women should not vote|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of hook and re-hooking your ex?",
                    "score": 0.6486,
                    "answers": "- hook and re - push your ex|conj\thook and re - push your ex|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Leal say to Hector?",
                    "score": 0.6205,
                    "answers": "To what Leal replied , ' Let me see , see if I understood , are you asking me if I would go back to my ex ?|ROOT\tLet me see , see if I understood , are you asking me if I would go back to my ex|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Hector and Leal?",
                    "score": 0.6193,
                    "answers": "back to my ex|advmod\tto my ex|prep\tmy ex|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "When he played the turn of Mexivergas, he commented.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eluniversal.com.mx report that he played the turn of Mexivergas?",
                    "answer": "02/12/2015"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who played Mexivergas?",
                    "score": 0.848,
                    "answers": "on 02/12/2015|prep\tthe turn of Mexivergas|dobj\tof Mexivergas|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who played the turn of Mexivergas?",
                    "score": 0.8143,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 02/12/2015 that When he played the turn of Mexivergas , he commented|ROOT\tthat|mark\tWhen|advmod\the|nsubj\tWhen he played the turn of Mexivergas|advcl\tthe|det\t,|punct\the|nsubj\tthat When he played the turn of Mexivergas , he commented|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the link between Mexivergas and Eluniversal?",
                    "score": 0.6572,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'We all know that Yoss is here because Caeli didn't want to come ', but he didn't agree with that, he added'If you were canceled a program on Telehit before it came out you wouldn't let that affect you 'and'Yosstop's talent is as real as his nose'.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why is Yoss here?",
                    "answer": "Caeli didn't want to come"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did Caeli want to come to the country?",
                    "score": 0.8634,
                    "answers": "on 02/12/2015|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Yoss say about the program being canceled?",
                    "score": 0.7889,
                    "answers": "you|nsubjpass\tyou|nsubj\tyou|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Yoss's talent?",
                    "score": 0.6694,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 02/12/2015 that ' We all know that Yoss is here because Caeli did n't want to come ' , but he did n't agree with that , he added'If you were canceled a program on Telehit before it came out you would n't let that affect you ' and'Yosstop 's talent is as real as his nose '|ROOT\t'|punct\t'|punct\ta|det\tyou would n't let that affect you ' and'Yosstop 's talent is as real as his nose '|ccomp\t'|punct\tand'Yosstop 's|poss\tand'Yosstop 's talent|nsubj\tand'Yosstop 's talent is as real as his nose '|ccomp\tas real as his nose|acomp\tas his nose|prep\this|poss\this nose|pobj\t'|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Yoss and Telehit?",
                    "score": 0.6297,
                    "answers": ", he added'If you were canceled a program on Telehit before it came out|punct\the added'If you were canceled a program on Telehit before it came out|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "About Alex Strucci, he said,'You're handsome, ma'am.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eluniversal.com.mx report that About Alex Strucci, he said, 'You're handsome, ma'am?",
                    "answer": "02/12/2015"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Alex Strucci's ethnicity?",
                    "score": 0.8485,
                    "answers": "handsome|acomp\tma'am|npadvmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Alex Strucci saying he is handsome, ma'am?",
                    "score": 0.8021,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 02/12/2015 that About Alex Strucci , he said,'You're handsome , ma'am|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Alex Strucci?",
                    "score": 0.7921,
                    "answers": "About Alex Strucci|prep\tAlex|compound\tthat About Alex Strucci , he said,'You're handsome , ma'am|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "and you've never read a book, you could be president.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eluniversal.com.mx report that if you've never read a book, you could be president?",
                    "answer": "02/12/2015"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many books can you read to become president?",
                    "score": 0.8937,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 02/12/2015 that and you 've never read a book , you could be president|ROOT\ta book|dobj\tcould|aux\tthat and you 've never read a book , you could be president|ccomp\tpresident|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many books have been published in the year 2015?",
                    "score": 0.8551,
                    "answers": "and you 've never read a book|parataxis"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of who could be president if they've never read a book?",
                    "score": 0.8112,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tand|cc\tyou|nsubj\t've|aux\ta|det\t,|punct\tyou|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Chumel said,'Chumel, have you told the story of how they saw your face?They told him I was going to study with Stephen Hawkin, they tricked him with a letter written in lousy English'.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What language was the letter written in?",
                    "answer": "lousy English'"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Chumel say to Stephen Hawkin?",
                    "score": 0.7951,
                    "answers": "said,'Chumel|npadvmod\twith a letter written in lousy English|prep\ta letter written in lousy English|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Chumel tell Stephen Hawkin about his face?",
                    "score": 0.7921,
                    "answers": "that Chumel said,'Chumel , have you told the story of how they saw your face?They|ccomp\tthe story of how they saw|dobj\tof how they saw|prep\thow they saw|pcomp\tyour face?They|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What language was the letter written in?",
                    "score": 0.752,
                    "answers": "written in lousy English|acl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who did Chumel tell he was going to study with?",
                    "score": 0.7424,
                    "answers": "told him I was going to study with Stephen Hawkin|ccomp\ttold him I was going to study with Stephen Hawkin , they tricked him with a letter written in lousy English '|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "To Werever, he said 'We thought your career was over when your manager let you down, but you came back and came back stronger than ever.. announcing BonIce ', 'Today WereverTumorro is so irrelevant that he even had to pay us to talk bad about him ', he concluded.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How did Werever feel about BonIce?",
                    "answer": "he even had to pay us to talk bad about him"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Bon Ice say to Werever?",
                    "score": 0.6645,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t,|punct\tWe|nsubj\tyour|poss\tyour|poss\tyou|dobj\t,|punct\tyou|nsubj\tyou came back and came back stronger than ever|conj\tback|advmod\tback|advmod\tthan ever|prep\t,|punct\tthat|mark\tto|aux\tus|dobj\tto|aux\thim|pobj\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did To Werever say about his manager letting her down?",
                    "score": 0.6264,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 02/12/2015 that To Werever , he said ' We thought your career was over when your manager let you down , but you came back and came back stronger than ever ..|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Bon Ice's career after he left the company?",
                    "score": 0.6024,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Bon Ice and Werever?",
                    "score": 0.5818,
                    "answers": "that To Werever , he said ' We thought your career was over when your manager let you down , but you came back and came back stronger than ever|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was Bon Ice's manager in 2015?",
                    "score": 0.5762,
                    "answers": "your manager|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the turn of Stracci, who was pointed out on multiple occasions for his undurable loving relationships and with people of the farandula, declared to his ex-girlfriend Yoss,'Yoss is also the pain of Huev.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Stracci say to his ex-girlfriend Yoss?",
                    "answer": "'Yoss is also the pain of Huev"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Stracci say about Yoss?",
                    "score": 0.6827,
                    "answers": "of Huev|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Stracci and Yoss?",
                    "score": 0.5984,
                    "answers": "who was pointed out on multiple occasions for his undurable loving relationships and with people of the farandula|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the pain of Huev?",
                    "score": 0.5537,
                    "answers": "is also the pain of Huev|ccomp\tthe pain of Huev|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Biggest 'and about the Werever Wero commented'you're the whitest shadow I've ever known'.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the site that reported that Werever Wero was 'the whitest shadow I ever known'?",
                    "answer": "Biggest"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the Werever Wero say about the black shadow?",
                    "score": 0.8328,
                    "answers": "that Biggest ' and about the Werever Wero commented'you're the whitest shadow I 've ever known '|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the significance of the Werever Wero?",
                    "score": 0.7554,
                    "answers": "Biggest ' and about the Werever|amod\tabout the Werever|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the black shadow that the Werever Wero said about humans?",
                    "score": 0.7474,
                    "answers": "ever|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the whitest shadow I've ever known?",
                    "score": 0.7314,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj\twww.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 02/12/2015|ROOT\ton 02/12/2015|prep\tI 've ever known|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the quotes from Werever Wero?",
                    "score": 0.7212,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t'|punct\tand|cc\tthe|det\tthe|det\tI|nsubj\t'|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Before starting participants and guests to the roast paraded on the blue carpet in which the most acclaimed were Galatzia and Werever, who did not hesitate to take pictures with their followers like everyone else.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did Galatzia and Werever take pictures with?",
                    "answer": "the most acclaimed were Galatzia and Werever, who did not hesitate to take pictures with their followers"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did Galatzia and Werever take pictures with followers like everyone else?",
                    "score": 0.6938,
                    "answers": "did|aux\tnot|neg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many followers did Galatzia and Werever have?",
                    "score": 0.6165,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj\ton 02/12/2015|prep\tthat|mark\tBefore starting|prep\tstarting|pcomp\tparticipants and guests to the roast|nsubj\tguests|conj\tto the roast|prep\tthe|det\tthe roast|pobj\tthat Before starting participants and guests to the roast paraded on the blue carpet in which the most acclaimed were Galatzia and Werever , who did not hesitate to take pictures with their followers like everyone else|ccomp\tthe|det\tin which|prep\twhich|pobj\tthe|det\tthe most acclaimed|nsubj\tto|aux\ttheir|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who took pictures with Galatzia and Werever?",
                    "score": 0.5885,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 02/12/2015 that Before starting participants and guests to the roast paraded on the blue carpet in which the most acclaimed were Galatzia and Werever , who did not hesitate to take pictures with their followers like everyone else|ROOT\tand|cc\ton the blue carpet in which the most acclaimed were Galatzia and Werever , who did not hesitate to take pictures with their followers like everyone else|prep\tthe blue carpet in which the most acclaimed were Galatzia and Werever , who did not hesitate to take pictures with their followers like everyone else|pobj\tmost|advmod\tin which the most acclaimed were Galatzia and Werever , who did not hesitate to take pictures with their followers like everyone else|relcl\tGalatzia and Werever , who did not hesitate to take pictures with their followers like everyone else|nsubj\tand|cc\t,|punct\twho|nsubj\twho did not hesitate to take pictures with their followers like everyone else|relcl\tto take pictures with their followers like everyone else|xcomp\tpictures|dobj\twith their followers|prep\ttheir followers|pobj\tlike everyone else|prep\teveryone else|pobj\telse|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Already inside the compound, Werever sat on the throne of the appointed and the others by his side to begin criticizing his companions.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did Werever sit when he began criticizing his companions?",
                    "answer": "on the throne of the appointed and the others"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Werever do with his companions?",
                    "score": 0.6837,
                    "answers": "to begin criticizing his companions|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where was Werever when he was inside the compound?",
                    "score": 0.6404,
                    "answers": "inside the compound|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the throne of the appointed?",
                    "score": 0.5667,
                    "answers": "the throne of the appointed|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Werever speaking out against his companions?",
                    "score": 0.562,
                    "answers": "his|poss\this|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Werever and his companions?",
                    "score": 0.5546,
                    "answers": "and|cc\tand the others|conj\tby his side|prep\this side|pobj\tcriticizing his companions|xcomp\this companions|dobj"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}